interface FrequentlyQuestions {
  question: string;
  answer: string;
}

export const frequentlyQuestions: FrequentlyQuestions[] = [
  {
    question: 'How can I search for recipes on your website?',
    answer: 'You can search for recipes using our search bar on the homepage or by exploring our recipe categories.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How can I find out what ingredients I need for a specific recipe?',
    answer: 'The required ingredients for each recipe are listed on the individual recipe page.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I submit my own recipes to be shared on your website?',
    answer:
      "Yes, we would love to see your recipes! Please submit your recipes using our contact form, and we'll review them for inclusion on our website if they meet our quality guidelines.",
  },
  {
    question: 'How can I get in touch with your team if I have a question or concern?',
    answer:
      "You can contact us through the 'Contact Us' page on our website or by emailing us at wlrp@example.com. We'll do our best to respond to your inquiry as soon as possible.",
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you ensure the quality and accuracy of the recipes on your website?',
    answer:
      'Our team carefully selects and tests each recipe before publishing it on our website. We also rely on user feedback to continually improve and update our content.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I use your recipes for commercial purposes?',
    answer:
      'No, our recipes are for personal use only and should not be used for commercial purposes without our written permission.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you offer nutritional information for your recipes?',
    answer:
      "Yes, nutritional information is available for most of our recipes. Simply scroll down to the 'Nutrition Information' section on each recipe page.",
  },
  {
    question: 'Are your recipes suitable for people with specific dietary needs?',
    answer:
      'We offer a range of recipes to suit different dietary needs, including vegan, vegetarian, gluten-free, and low-carb options. However, we recommend that you consult with a medical professional before making any significant changes to your diet.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I modify your recipes to suit my tastes?',
    answer:
      'Of course! We encourage you to experiment with our recipes and make them your own. However, please note that we cannot guarantee the results if you make significant modifications to the original recipe.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I save recipes to access offline?',
    answer:
      'Unfortunately, we do not currently offer an offline saving feature. However, you can bookmark our website on your device to access it easily in the future.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do you have a mobile app for your recipes?',
    answer:
      'We currently do not have a mobile app, but our website is optimized for mobile viewing. Simply visit our website on your mobile device to access our recipes on the go.',
  },
];
